<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Colorado Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome to Colorado!</string>
    <string name="lake_activity_text">Lakes</string>
    <string name="breweries_activity_text">Breweries</string>
    <string name="restaurants_activity_text">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="attractions_activity_text">Attractions</string>
    <string name="bluemesalakedescription">Located in Western Colorado near the town of Gunnison, Colorado’s largest body of water is a must-see destination. Blue Mesa Reservoir spans 20 miles and boasts over 96 miles of shoreline.</string>
    <string name="dillonreservoirdescription">Dillon Reservoir, sometimes referred to as Lake Dillon, is a large fresh water reservoir located in Summit County, Colorado, south of I-70 and bordered by the towns of Frisco, Silverthorne, and Dillon.</string>
    <string name="hanginglakedescription">Hanging Lake is a lake in the U.S. State of Colorado. It is located in Glenwood Canyon, about 7 miles east of Glenwood Springs, Colorado and is a popular tourist destination.</string>
    <string name="grandlakedescription">Located at the headwaters of the Colorado River and situated on the shores of Grand Lake, Colorado\'s largest natural body of water, the Town of Grand Lake is the western gateway to Rocky Mountain National Park.</string>
    <string name="echolakedescription">Colorado’s Echo Lake is looped by an easy hiking trail and serves as a trailhead to even more classic Colorado hikes.</string>
    <string name="craterlakedescription">Crater Lake is a mountain lake in the Elk Mountains, Pitkin County of the US State of Colorado. It lies just northeast of the Maroon Bells and just northwest of Pyramid Peak.</string>
    <string name="dreamlakedescription">The hike to Dream Lake is one of the popular destination hikes in Rocky Mountain National Park–and for good reason. In the early morning hours, Dream Lake is a vision straight out of a fairy tale.</string>
    <string name="tenbarrelbrewerydescription"><![CDATA[Sprawling brewpub serving several house beers alongside inventive pizzas, burgers & bar snacks.]]></string>
    <string name="avalanchebrewerydescription">The Avalanche Brewing Company has been brewing beer amongst the mighty San Juan Mountains in Silverton, Colorado since late 2011. Their beers are the obsession of owner and brewmaster Austin Lashley.</string>
    <string name="averybrewererydescription"><![CDATA[Serving house beers including some offbeat styles & a brewpub menu plus tours & dog-friendly patio.]]></string>
    <string name="bluemoonbrewerydescription"><![CDATA[Modern American food & beer served in a cavernous brewery with flashy decor & a large patio.]]></string>
    <string name="breckenridgebrewerydescription"><![CDATA[Brewery & tasting room serving craft beers, plus an on-site restaurant cooking hearty American fare.]]></string>
    <string name="boulderbeerbrewerydescription"><![CDATA[Established microbrewery offering free tours & beer samples, a tavern serving pub grub & more.]]></string>
    <string name="drydockbrewerydescription"><![CDATA[Popular craft brewery with a lively, relaxed taproom plus social happenings & a patio.]]></string>
    <string name="rootdownrestaurantdescription">A converted filling station is an artful, high-energy venue for creative American small plates.</string>
    <string name="sushidenrestaurantdescription">Fish is flown in daily from Tokyo at this hopping venue with lots of people watching.</string>
    <string name="snoozerestaurantdescription">Snooze an AM Eatery, a breakfast and lunch restaurant and eatery focused on energetic atmosphere, engaging service and above all innovative.</string>
    <string name="lingerrestaurantdescription"><![CDATA[This old mortuary is now a lively restaurant with a rooftop lounge & global small plates.]]></string>
    <string name="amblirestaurantdescription"><![CDATA[Minimalist wine bar in a strip mall offering global tapas & prepared meals along with pairings.]]></string>
    <string name="riojarestaurantdescription"><![CDATA[Locally sourced, imaginative Mediterranean dishes & wines in a high-energy dining room.]]></string>
    <string name="oceanprimerestaurantdescription"><![CDATA[Upscale chain known for its sophisticated decor, long wine list & classic steak & seafood menu.]]></string>
    <string name="blackcanyonattractiondescription">Black Canyon of the Gunnison National Park is in western Colorado. It surrounds part of a deep, steep-walled gorge carved through Precambrian rock by the Gunnison River.</string>
    <string name="gardenofthegodsattractiondescription">Garden of the Gods is a public park located in Colorado Springs, Colorado, US. It was designated a National Natural Landmark in 1971.</string>
    <string name="redrocksattractiondescription">Red Rocks Amphitheatre is a rock structure near Morrison, Colorado, 10 miles west of Denver, where concerts are given in the open-air amphitheatre.</string>
    <string name="denverartmuseumattractiondescription">The Denver Art Museum — DAM is an art museum located in the Civic Center of Denver, Colorado. The museum is one of the largest art museums between the West Coast and Chicago.</string>
    <string name="cheyennemtattractiondescription">Cheyenne Mountain Zoo is America\'s ONLY AZA-accredited mountain zoo. It is located southwest of downtown Colorado Springs, Colorado, on Cheyenne Mountain in the United States and has an elevation of 6,800 feet above sea level.</string>
    <string name="sevenfallsattractiondescription">The Broadmoor Seven Falls is a series of seven cascading waterfalls of South Cheyenne Creek in South Cheyenne Cañon, Colorado Springs, Colorado. It is a privately owned tourist attraction since it was opened in the early 1880s.</string>
    <string name="denveraquariumattractiondescription"><![CDATA[Sprawling complex with a state-of-the-art aquarium housing 500+ species, plus a restaurant & lounge.]]></string>
    <string name="name_placeholder">Name</string>
    <string name="blackcanyonname">Black Canyon</string>
    <string name="gardenofthegodsname">Garden of the Gods</string>
    <string name="redrocksamphitheatername">Red Rocks Amphitheater</string>
    <string name="denverartmuseumname">Denver Art Museum</string>
    <string name="cheyennemtzooname">Cheyenne Mt. Zoo</string>
    <string name="sevenfallsname">Seven Falls</string>
    <string name="denveraquariumname">Denver Aquarium</string>
    <string name="tenbarrelbrewername">10 Barrel Brewery</string>
    <string name="avalanchebreweryname">Avalanche Brewery</string>
    <string name="averybrewereryname">Avery Brewery</string>
    <string name="bluemoonbreweryname">Blue Moon Brewery</string>
    <string name="breckenridgebreweryname">Breckenridge Brewery</string>
    <string name="boulderbeerbreweryname">Boulder Beer Company</string>
    <string name="drydockbreweryname">Dry Dock Brewery</string>
    <string name="bluemesalakename">Blue Mesa Reservoir</string>
    <string name="dillonreservoirname">Dillon Reservoir</string>
    <string name="hanginglakename">Hanging Lake</string>
    <string name="grandlakename">Grand Lake</string>
    <string name="echolakename">Echo Lake</string>
    <string name="craterlakename">Crater Lake</string>
    <string name="dreamlakename">Dream Lake</string>
    <string name="rootdownrestaurantname">Root Down</string>
    <string name="sushidenrestaurantname">Sushi Den</string>
    <string name="snoozerestaurantname">Snooze</string>
    <string name="lingerrestaurantname">Linger</string>
    <string name="amblirestaurantname">Ambli</string>
    <string name="riojarestaurantname">Rioja</string>
    <string name="oceanprimerestaurantname">Ocean Prime</string>
    <string name="intentplaceimage">Place Image</string>
    <string name="intentplacedescription">Place Description</string>
    <string name="intentplacename">Place Name</string>
</resources>
